https://www.converters.tv/privacy-policy.html

[Skip to Content]
Contact Us
Email :
Password :
Analog Audio Converters
Analog Audio to Analog ...
Analog Audio to Digita ...
Analog Audio to HDTV C ...
Digital Audio to Analo ...
USB 2.0 to Analog Audi ...
HDTV to Analog Audio C ...
Digital Audio Converters
Digital Audio to Analo ...
Digital Audio to Digit ...
Digital Audio to HDTV
...
Analog Audio to Digita ...
USB 2.0 to Digital Aud ...
HDTV to Digital Audio
...
USB 2.0 Converters
USB 2.0 to Analog Audi ...
USB 2.0 to Digital Aud ...
USB 2.0 to USB 2.0 Con ...
HDTV Converters
HDTV to Analog Audio C ...
HDTV to Digital Audio
...
HDTV to VGA+ Converters
Analog Audio to HDTV C ...
CGA to HDTV Converters
Digital Audio to HDTV
...
Introduction
Converters.tv is committed to protecting your privacy and we provide this privacy policy statement to assure you of our sincerity in this matter. By visiting Converters.tv, you hereby accept this Privacy Policy and accept the practices described herein. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information.
What Personal Information does Converters.tv collect??
Information you give us
During the membership registration process we require specific personal information to be provided before membership is successfully completed. This information is as follows:NameEmail AddresssAddreess (Street Address, City, State, Country, Zip/Post Code)Phone NumberThe information is used for two purposes only :Firstly, any personal information collected about you through during membership registration is used primarily for the purpose of processing orders. Information such as name and address are stored for shipping purposes. The information is stored to adequately respond to your requests, to customise future shopping for you, and to communicate with you.Secondly, the personal information that is collected by Converters.tv during membership registration is used to help us provide a better service for our members. Personal information, such as geographic location, is used to assist us in offering special offers, providing information about local events, etc.When you become a member on Converters.tv, you can use this account across all Highway Group websites. This includes Highway Games, Highway Entertainment, and Car Converters. Please not that if you visit these sites, you are bound by the Terms and Conditions of that particular Website.NO PERSONAL INFORMATION IS PROVIDED TO ANY THIRD PARTY WITHOUT EXPRESS PERMISSION.
Optional Information
In addition to the personal information that is gathered during the registration, members have the option of providing us with additional information, such as their business interests, and user preferences. This information is used solely to allow us to provide our newsletters and offers to members who wish to receive them.THIS INFORMATION IS, UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES, PROVIDED TO ANY THIRD PARTY WITHOUT YOUR EXPRESS PERMISSION.
Automatic Information
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Like many Web sites, we also use "cookies". Cookies are small data files stored on your hard disk which provide information back to our server. The use of cookies on Converters.tv allows our systems to recognise your browser and to provide certain features for you, such as automatic login and remembering a member's preferences.Converters.tv also maintains a record of user IP addresses for the purposes of diagnosing problems with our server, and to assist in website administration. We also use it to gather broad demographic information about our users in general and in no manner use an IP address to collect personal information about any individual user.
Credit Card Information
CONVERTERS.TV DOES NOT STORE MEMBERS CREDIT CARD INFORMATION. Our credit card payments are processed directly between the user and our bank, and as such, we do not have access to credit card information provided by the user throughout this process.
Newsletters and Email
All members of Converters.tv have the option of receiving our newsletters and e-mails announcing special offers, recent site updates, current industry news, and so on. This is entirely optional and members are able to change their preferences at any time to stop receiving these. Users are able to become a member on Converters.tv and choose not to receive our newsletters and e-mails.The only email that all members will automatically receive is the initial registration email providing a member password. Additionally, members may be contacted by Converters.tv if they are in violation of our Terms and Agreements Statement.CONVERTERS.TV WILL NEVER SEND ANY UNSOLICITED E-MAILS OR PROVIDE YOUR E-MAIL ADDRESS TO ANY THIRD PARTY WITHOUT YOUR EXPRESS PERMISSION.
Control of Your Password
Members are responsible for all actions taken with their User ID and password, including those actions that result in fees being charged to your account. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your password to any third parties. All user passwords are encrypted (using the MD5 encryption algorithm) by Converters.tv, which means that passwords are not viewable or accessible by Converters.tv staff. Additionally this means that Converters.tv staff cannot change a user's password. If the user forgets their password, it is their responsibility to reset their password using the link on the "Login" section of the Converters.tv website.
Surveys
Occasionally Converters.tv may conduct surveys to assist us in providing you with a better website featuring information and services that members would like to have on our website. Completing surveys is optional and any information collected from our surveys is not provided to any third party whatsoever.
External Links
Converters.tv provides links to external sites on many of our pages. Converters.tv has no control over such sites and accepts no responsibility for the privacy policy and practices of any site other than Converters.tv.
Amendment
We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy will be reviewed and, if appropriate, updated from time to time so that it accurately reflects the regulatory environment and our own data collection and disclosures practices.
Quick Search
News
Latest Products
Specials
Stock List
Contact Us
Payment Options
Copyright 2001-2020, Converters.tv Pty Ltd. All rights reserved. Converters.tv is part of the Highway Group Pty. Ltd. network
Trademarks, brands, patents are the property of their respective owners. Use of this website constitutes acceptance of the Converters.tv User Agreement and Privacy Policy.
Our Other Sites:
